A Guide to the Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1974-2006.
Library of Virginia
- Correspondence and subject files of the Virginia Superintendent of Public Instruction (Accession 39607), 1974-2006., Extent: xx boxes. (Box 1-xx)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1982-1983.
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Importance of Reading in Virginia - Present and Future, 1983 Jan. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Technical Assistance for Equity Seminar, 1983. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Technology interview, 1983 Jan. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Gladys PTA, 1983 Feb. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): National Association of Children with Learning Disabilities, 1983 Feb. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Governor's Commission on Virginia's Future - Primary and Secondary Education in Virginia Current Trends and Future Developments, 1983 Mar. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Health Occupations Students of America, 1983 Mar. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Chapter I Conference - A Better Tomorrow for Today's Children, 1983 Mar. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Virginia Community Education Association - The Community Role in the Educational Plan for Virginia, 1983 Apr. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Comments on the Report of the National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1983 Apr. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Danforth School Board Program, 1983 May. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Dedication - Giles Co. School, 1983 May. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Brunswick Co. Awards Banquet, 1983 May. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Lynchburg Association of Educational Secretaries, 1983 June. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Graduation Exercise, Chesterfield Co. (Clover Hill H.S.), 1983. (Box 23b)
    - Speeches (S. John Davis): Migrant Education In-Service Training, 1983 June. (Box 23b)
    - Wives of State Officials (Mrs. Davis), 1982-1983. (Box 23b)
    - Correspondence (S. John Davis), 1982. (Box 23b)
    - Correspondence (S. John Davis), 1983. (Box 23b)
    - Nelson, Maggie, 1982-1983. (Box 23b)
    - Agricultural Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Audio-visual materials, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1982 Dec. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1983 Jan. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1983 Feb. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1983 Mar. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1983 Apr. (Box 24a)
    - Budget/Funding, 1983 May-June. (Box 24a)
    - Career Education, 1982-198. (Box 24a)
    - Driver Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - ECIA Chapter I, 1982. (Box 24a)
    - ECIA Chapter I, 1983. (Box 24a)
    - Employee Advisory Committee, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Facilities, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Cale, M., 1982 June-Aug. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Cale, M., 1982 Sept-Oct. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Director, 1982. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Director, 1983. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Budget Office, 1982 Sept-Oct. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Budget Office, 1982 Nov-Dec. (Box 24a)
    - Financial and Administrative Services - Budget Office, 1983. (Box 24a)
    - Finance public education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Fine Arts Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Foreign Language Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Gifted Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Guidance Counseling, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Instructional Media and Technology, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Internal Audit Survey, 1986. (Box 24a)
    - Major Programs of Study Project, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Michie Committee recommendations, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Music Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Professional Development, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Proprietary Schools, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Public Information and Publications, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Pupil Transportation Services, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Reading / Reading Month, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Reihm, Carl, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - School Food Service, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Science Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Secondary Schools, 1982-1983. (Box 24a)
    - Shingleton, Callie, 1982. (Box 24b)
    - Shingleton, Callie, 1983. (Box 24b)
    - Special Education, 1982. (Box 24b)
    - Special Education, 1983. (Box 24b)
    - Technical Assistance for Equity in Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24b)
    - Teacher Certification, 1982-1983. (Box 24b)
    - Virginia is for Equity in Education - Grant, 1982-1983. (Box 24b)
    - Vocational Education, 1982-1983. (Box 24b)
  - Correspondence and subject files (Dr. S. John Davis), 1983-1984.
    - A - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - American Association of School Administrators, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Annual Conference of Division Superintendents, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Appalachia Education Labs, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Albemarle County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Alexandria, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Alleghany County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Amelia County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Amherst County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Appomattox County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Arlington County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Augusta County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - B - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Bath County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Bedford City, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Bedford County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Bland County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Botetourt County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Bristol, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Brunswick County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Buchanan County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Buckingham County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Buena Vista, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - C - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Centex - Center for Excellence, Inc., 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Colleges and Universities (Virginia), 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Colleges and Universities (Out of state), 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - community Colleges, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Campbell County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Cape Charles, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Caroline County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Carroll County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Charles City County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Charlotte County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Charlottesville, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Chesapeake, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Chesterfield County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Colonial Heights, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Covington, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Craig County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Culpeper County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Cumberland County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - D - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Developmental Disabilities Protection and Advocacy Office, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Danville, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Dickenson County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Dinwiddie County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - E - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Education Commission of the States, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Education Testing Service, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - Education - NTE meeting, 1984 May. (Box 25a)
    - Essex County, 1983-1984. (Box 25a)
    - F - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Fairfax County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Falls Church, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Fauquier County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Floyd County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Fluvanna County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Franklin City, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Franklin County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Frederick County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Fredericksburg, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - G - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - General Assembly - House of Delegates, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - General Assembly - Senate, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - General Assembly - Other states, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Governor's Commission on the Future, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Governor's Magnet Schools for Science and Technology, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Galax, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Giles County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - gloucester County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Goochland County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Grayson County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Greensville County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - H - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Halifax County - South Boston, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Hampton, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Hanover County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Harrisonburg, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Henrico County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Henry County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Highland County, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - Hopewell, 1983-1984. (Box 25b)
    - I - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Impact aid, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - isle of Wight, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - J - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Jobs for Virginia Graduates, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - K - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Keep Virginia Beautiful, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - King George County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - King and Queen County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - King William County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - L - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Lancaster County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Lee County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Lexington, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Loudoun County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Louisa County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Lunenburg County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Lynchburg, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - M - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Madison County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Manassas, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Manassas Park, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Martinsville, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Mathews County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Mecklenburg County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Middlesex County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Montgomery County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - N - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - National Association of State Boards of Education, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - National Commission on Excellence in Education, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - National Forest receipts, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - National Teacher Examinations and Policy Council, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Nelson County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - New Kent County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Newport News, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Norfolk, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Northampton County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Northumberland County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Nottoway County, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - O- Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - P - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Personnel Newsletter (DOE), 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Presidential Academic Fitness Awards Program, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Presidential Awards for Excellence, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Presidential Scholars Program, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Procurement Act, 1983-1984. (Box 27a)
    - Page County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Poquoson, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Portsmouth, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Powhatan County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Prince Edward County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Prince George County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Prince William County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Pulaski County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Q - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - R - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Register of Regulations, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Radford, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Rappahannock County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Richmond City, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Richmond County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Roanoke City, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Roanoke County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Rockbridge County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Rockingham County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Russell County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - S - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Secondary School Recognition Program, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Southeastern Cooperative Education Program, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - State Departments of Education - Other states, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - State-Ed (newsletter), 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - State Employee Credit Union, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - State Special Education Advisory Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Superintendent's Advisory Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Superintendent's Employyee Advisory Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Superintendent's study groups, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Superintendent - School board relations, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Salem, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Shenandoah County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Smyth County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - South Boston, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Southampton County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Spotsylvania County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Stafford County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Staunton, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Suffolk, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Surry County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - Sussex County, 1983-1984. (Box 27b)
    - T - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Tayloe Murphy Institute, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Tuition Assistance Advisory Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Tazewell County, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Congress, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Block grants (Chapter II), 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office for Civil Rights, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Dept. of Education - Office of Special Education, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Secretary of Education, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Campaign, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - V - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities (VACLD), 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Schools, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Association of Independent Special Education Facilities, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Association of School Administrators (VASA), 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Association of Secondary School Principals, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Community College System, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Congress of Parents and Teachers, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Council of Health and Medical Care, Inc., 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Council of School Administrators, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Education Association, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia High School League, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Manufacturers Association, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia Public School Authority, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia School Boards Association, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind (Hampton and Staunton), 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind - Hampton, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia School for the Deaf and Blind - Staunton, 1983-1984. (Box 28a)
    - Virginia State Advisory Council on Vocational Education, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Virginia State Library, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Virginia Beach, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - W - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Washington County, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Waynesboro, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - West Point, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Williamsburg, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Winchester, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Wise County, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Wythe County, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - X - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Y - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - York County, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - Z - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 28b)
    - State Government: Aging, Dept. for the, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Agriculture, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Appropriations Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Attorney General, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Auditor of Public Accounts, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Aviation, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Children, Division of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Comptroller's Office, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Conservation and Economic Development, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Council on Higher Education, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Criminal Justice Services, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Employment Commission, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: General Services, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Executive Orders, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Governor's Office - Virginia Liaison Office, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Health Dept., 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Highway Dept., 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Joint Legislative Audit and Review Commission, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government: Legislative Services, Division of, 1983-1984. (Box 29a)
    - State Government:, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Management Analysis and Systems Development, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Mental Health and Mental Retardation, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Miscellaneous State Agencies, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Motor Vehicles, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Personnel and Training, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Registrar of Regulations (Virginia Code Commission), 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative School Authority, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Secretary of Commerce and Resources, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Secretary of the Commonwealth, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Education (5 folders), 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Human Affairs, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Public Safety, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Secretary of Transportation, 1983-1984. (Box 29b)
    - State Government: Social Services, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: State Agency Luncheon Group, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: State Water Control Board - State Water Plan Advisory Committee, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Taxation, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Telecommunications, Dept. of, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - State Government: Virginia Supplemental Retirement System, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Correspondence, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Recommendations, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Dedication of Special Education Vocational Center at Marshall High School - S. John Davis Center), 1983 Sept 11. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Teacher Education Forum), 1983 Nov 3-4. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Dept. of Education, Professional Women), 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Norfolk State University - Mid-Year Faculty Conference), 1984 Jan 4. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Community College Administrators - Community Education), 1984 Mar 13. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (State High School Athletic Directors), 1984 Apr 6. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (League of Women Voters), 1984 Apr 11. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Henrico County Schools - Distributive Education Dept.), 1984 May 2. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Division Superintendents Annual Conference), 1984 May. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (State Chamber of Commerce Education Committee), 1984 May 15. (Box 30a)
    - S. John Davis - Speeches (Virginia Educational Research Association), 1984 May 17. (Box 30a)
    - Mrs. S. John Davis - Wives of state officials, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Governor's Employment and Training Council, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Governor's Advisory Committee on Child Abuse, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Governor's Special Advisory Committee on Merit Pay for Teachers, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Governor's Task Force on Drug Abuse, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - GSpecial Assistant Public Information Publications, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Administrative Director - Board/Staff Relations, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Block Grant - Chapter II, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Deputy Superintendent - William H. Cochran, 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Deputy Superintendent - William H. Cochran (Recommendations), 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Deputy Superintendent - William H. Cochran (Regional Schools - Committee Administering Teacher Scholarships), 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Deputy Superintendent - William H. Cochran (Institute of Government - UVA), 1983-1984. (Box 30a)
    - Administrative Services Division, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Administrative Services - Planning and Evaluation, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Management Information Services Division Director, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Research Evaluation and Testing Division Director, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Associate Director - Testing, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Associate Director - Innovative Program, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Elementary School Accreditation, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Supervisor - Secondary School Accreditation, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Supervisor - School Evaluation, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Associate Superintendent of Personnel and Administration - Field Services, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Administrative Director of Personnel and Professional Development, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Beginning Teacher Assistance Program (BTAP), 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Governor's Task Force on Master Teacher Plan and Career Ladder / Pay for Performance Plans, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Division of Technical Assistance, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Teacher Education / Certification, 1983-1984. (Box 30b)
    - Director of Personnel, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Personnel - Policy/Administrative, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Professional Development, Division of, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Professional Development, Division of - Survey of interest in business and industry, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Community Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Associate Superintendent of Curriculum and Instruction, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - General Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Governor's Conference on Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Shingleton - Magnet Schools / Science and Technology, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Varina High School - Governor's Center for Educational Innovation and Technology / Action Team, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Governor's Economic Development Projects (Dr. Callie Shingleton), 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Rural School Effectiveness Project, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Sciences and Elementary Administration, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Health, Physical Education and Driver's Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Mathematics, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Science, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Humanities and Secondary Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Secondary Education, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Lanuguages, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Social Studies, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)
    - Fine Arts, 1983-1984. (Box 31a)